

Good knowledge of

- JavaScript
- React
- Hooks
- Redux
- CSS & HTML
- CSS modules
- Git
- NPM
- Next.js
- SEO
- API

Basic knowledge of

- TypeScript
- Tailwind
- SCSS
- Bootstrap
- Firebase
- GraphQL

Non-Technical skills

- Working directly with the customer
- Running projects
- Communication and teamwork
- Task management

Language

- English B2
- Polish native

I hereby give consent for my personal data included in my application to be processed for the purposes of the recruitment process under the European Parliament's and Council of the European Union Regulation on the Protection of Natural Persons as of 27 April 2016, with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC.

Arkadiusz Wojciechowski

Seo Specialist/Aspiring Front-end Developer

As an SEO specialist with one year of experience, I am seeking a new opportunity to transition into a junior frontend developer role or other junior position with a focus on Web Development. I am passionate about developing my skills and willing to work hard to achieve my goals. With a strong work ethic and dedication to continuous learning, I am confident that I can make a valuable contribution to any team.

Contact





+48 664 459 763 arkadiusz.r.wojciechowski@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/arkadiusz-wojciechowski



https://github.com/Voyar1

Projects

Hynext - modern blog app Next.js, React, CSS modules, ES6+, graphalrequest, hygraph



Hynext - GitHub

The project is a web application that functions as a blog, created using the Next.js framework with Hygraph content management system. The blog application created using Next.is and Hygraph provides a powerful and flexible platform for creating and publishing blog content. Users can create and manage blog posts, add images and other media. The application also includes search engine optimization features and is optimized for performance (PSI)

Personal portfolio website

React, CSS, ES6+, email.js, react-scroll



Portfolio - GitHub

It provides a clean and modern design, with features such as a responsive layout, smooth animations, and interactive elements that enhance the user experience. The website includes sections for displaying information about the developer's work experience, skills, and projects. One of the benefits of using React for this project is the ability to easily update and maintain the website's content. The website can be updated with new projects and achievements without requiring extensive changes to the underlying codebase.

Experience

09.2022 - Present

Kerris Group

SEO Specialist

I am responsible for managing and executing various projects for client websites to improve their organic search visibility and traffic. This involves conducting a thorough audit of the website, identifying areas of improvement, and creating a tailored SEO strategy that aligns with the client's goals. I also collaborate with various people, including web developers, content writers, and social media managers, to ensure that the SEO strategy is effectively integrated across all online channels.

06-09.2022

Grupa iCEA

Junior SEO Specialist

I played a key role in supporting the SEO team in implementing and optimizing SEO strategies for clients. In this role, I conduct keyword research and perform on-page optimization, and I analyzed website performance metrics to make data-driven recommendations for improving organic search visibility and traffic.

11.2021-03.2022

NPROFIT

Junior SEO Specialist

Education

10.2017 - 02.2021

3 years 5 months

Poznan University of Technology

Area of study: Logistics of transport

Title: Engineer